Hey, how's it going guys?
And welcome to the advanced direct response Video Edit Editor training.
I know a lot of you guys have been waiting for this,
so I'm super stoked to jump in this and start giving you guys some value. Um,
so let's just jump straight into this, um, what you guys are gonna be learning.
And who is this for? Primarily, it's for video editors, videographers,
video makers, video marketers, agency owners, and brand owners. Okay?
If you're dealing with creative and you're working in Premier Pro or you're
creating social content or you're creating ads,
this training is going to make you a better editor, a better marketer,
a better, uh, direct response editor. Uh,
it's going to make you more aware of a lot of different techniques as well
as skills. Um, so we're gonna break that down right now.
So what you'll gain from taking this program is strategy,
technique as well as emotional and mental,
I would say skills and resources to,
to use and apply to level yourself up. Okay? So when we talk about strategy,
you're gonna understand the why behind direct response marketing and also the
exact high performance methods we use at our creative agency at econ vids.
Number two, uh, when it comes to technique,
you're gonna learn how to actually make high converting direct response video
ads that generate seven to eight figures for our clients. And lastly,
when it comes to emotional mental health, uh,
you're gonna learn the wisdom to be emotionally and mentally resilient
and effective as an editor,
because I believe all three of these areas and domains are the key to
actually leveling yourself up as a creative, as an editor, as a marketer,
all those things that are, are all in sync with each other. So, um,
this is a very tentative program overview. This is going to change, I'm sure,
as the program develops and evolves.
But just to give you guys a little bit of a overview, macro view,
you're gonna learn direct response video. You're gonna learn, you know, right?
Equipment, benefits and features and angles, scripts, brand research,
asset libraries, inspiration, flow ad testing, uh,
video editing techniques, of course,
applying data to your creative resources and all that good stuff.
So here is an actual mind map of what I was able to just brain dump
that this course will include. So if you've never heard of me,
you've never seen me, you've never met me, nice to meet you.
My name is actually John Felix Reyes,
and I am the creator and founder of Ads Rx,
as well as a seven figure video production company called Econ.
Over the last four and a half, almost five years now,
we've shot well over 7,000 video ads for e-comm brands,
those who are running Facebook ads, YouTube ads, TikTok ads, and uh,
I've have over 10 years direct response marketing experience.
So before this, I wasn't just a video guy,
actually very recently became a video guy. I was actually a graphic designer.
I had multiple different companies, e-commerce businesses,
Amazon supplements, drop shipping. I've done it all,
and it led me to this path of becoming a creative entrepreneur, which,
um, now I own my own video production company and team, and I manage, uh,
over 10 people right now. But I used to have a much larger team.
And throughout this whole journey, I really just taught myself.
I learned by trial and error. I made a lot of mistakes and a lot of fuckups,
and I've lost a lot of money, but it made me the person I am today,
and it gave me all the wisdom that I know today.
So this is the kind of stuff that, you know, you can't learn in a book,
you learn through experience. And by taking this course,
I'm just gonna be passing down my wisdom, my trial and error, and my experience,
uh, to make your life a lot easier. And lastly, I love comedy.
I love entertaining.
So you might hear a couple bad jokes here and there throughout the presentation.
So if it's not funny, don't laugh, it's not funny. Okay? Alright,
so quick story about me, uh,
on the picture on the left is actually in 2016 where I thought Lambos were
super, super cool. Uh, I still think they're cool, but I really,
really wanted one.
And so this picture I took where I rented a Lamborghini for a whole day.
I was living the fast life.
I was this bachelor who was quote unquote crushing it, doing very well,
living in the premium spot in Orange County, you know, partying,
drinking girls drugs, you name it, all of that.
And so I was this really, really reckless guy and I made a ton of money,
and then I freaking lost it all. Um,
my partners in my previous business, which was, um,
close to becoming an eight figure business,
found out that I was parting and I wasn't really applying any of
my time to the business.
And what happened was they kicked me out of my own company. So,
long story short, um, I basically had to move everything.
I lost, you know, my h not my home,
but I moved everything out and I had to downsize and
move into this like, crappy one bedroom apartment.
So it was this huge identity shift that really screwed
me for a long time. And I had to rebuild myself from the ground up.
And that was an entire learning journey for myself coming
from this like total d****e area,
d****e lifestyle to becoming who I am today, uh,
where I am now, a father, and I have two boys, and, uh,
they're crazy.
And that life is a completely different one compared to what I was living
before. So if you have kids, you can totally relate. Uh, if you don't have kids,
you can probably still relate because life is fun without kids. Alright,
here's a, a couple little photos of flashback.
When I used to have a really big team, uh,
I used to have a fairly large studio,
production studio where we would shoot hundreds of videos a month.
I'm telling you, hundreds. We were like clockwork, uh,
producing content every single day for hundreds of clients. Uh,
here's some sets that we build,
we custom built and we would change these out every single month or so,
and we're constantly developing new, new looks and, and whatnot. And it was,
it was a lot of fun. It was a lot of fun. Um, yeah, here's some sales. You know,
in the last, since 2018, we've done over five and a half, like almost 5.2,
two 6 million, whatever. Uh, here's some sales that we've generated.
Just one client, actually. So that's half a million in one month. So,
um, yeah, we've done a lot. You know, it's,
it's nothing here to show off or brag. I just let you know, like I've,
I've done a ton of stuff, uh,
I've gone through the ringer and this is kind of where
all that wisdom is accumulated into, into this course.
So why does this matter to you? All right?
So I broke this down into five little steps. First off,
this stuff isn't taught anywhere, okay? Like I'm telling you,
this is stuff that you, you either learn by doing it,
you either learn by being mentored by somebody,
or paying a ton of money to go to a mastermind.
'cause these are things that YouTube videos just aren't gonna teach you.
So the benefit of this is you'll be getting access to 10 years of my experience
as a creative entrepreneur, just a lot of time. Uh, number two,
you're gonna increase your skill sets. That is for sure a given.
So when you increase your skill sets, uh,
you'll be a better direct response marketer. You'll be a better editor,
you'll be better at strategy, and you'll be way more efficient. Number three,
you're gonna save a s**t ton of time. All right? I, I love saving time.
So you're gonna learn all the shortcuts I use to become super efficient and
have a way better creative workflow.
'cause I'm a dad and I run 2, 2, 3 different companies.
So time for me is so freaking important. And if I'm not saving time,
then I'm killing time and I don't like that. So number four,
you're gonna get better results, all right? So whether you're on a team,
own your own business,
you're gonna be able to create way high converting content,
way more high converting content,
because you're gonna actually learn the why behind stuff.
You're not just gonna be throwing stuff out there, wasting time,
wasting editing.
This is gonna teach you principles as well as technique and strategy because you
need all of that to have a complete understanding of how this stuff works.
Number five, you are gonna be way more valuable, okay?
So whether you have an agency, you're gonna be able to keep more clients,
you're gonna be able to attract more clients. Uh, if you work in a team,
you're gonna be able to increase your own skillset and experience.
You're gonna be able to get a raise, get promoted,
and start maybe even leading a team or managing a team. Um,
and or even become, you know,
a creative strategist and oversee different editors.
There's so many potentials here,
but the missing key to your growth is really skillsets
experience, so that you can problem solve at a much higher level.
'cause that's really what it comes down to. So, real quick,
I wanna address why most people fail. Okay?
So here's six reasons why most people fail at direct response video or video
editing, or trying to create high converting ads, so to speak.
Number one. Number one, you're not consistently learning and growing,
okay? Uh, I've worked with dozens of people, dozens of people, all right?
I had a team of 50 at one point,
and just showing up and doing the job and not striving to be any more
than just that.
And you're just happy to get a paycheck is the reason why you are not growing,
okay? That is why you are failing,
because you're just coasting by life and you are just
signing in, signing out, getting a paycheck and going on with your life.
That is how you stay mediocre and average. And that's not what you want, okay?
That's why you invested in this course, because you want to increase your value,
you wanna get smarter, you wanna get sharper, whatever. Number two,
you're only doing one aspect of the entire creative as the creative process that
should be actually. So when you're just editing or you're just copywriting,
or you're just shooting videos, you,
you need to experience all of it to get a much better understanding of how all
the pieces work together, okay?
So if you're just seeing the post-production side,
it's gonna be limiting for you because you are not exposed to the copywriting
side, which is like the straight, the,
the strategy and the the creative and the copy, which is the research phase,
right? And if you're just assembling clips,
then you're just gonna be primarily used as a executor,
and you wanna be an executor and a strategist at the same time,
because that's when you actually increase your worth in a company or as an
entrepreneur. Number three, you're not learning from the data, okay?
You're just following instructions.
You're not thinking about why something worked or why something didn't work.
And this is so, so important because as a performance marketer,
your job is to continually get better and understand more
of who your target audience is every single time you put out an ad.
Because it's almost like every time you learn something,
you get closer and closer to becoming more precise with your message,
more precise, with your creative. And it's not this guessing game anymore, okay?
So if you're not learning from the data,
you're just doing something different every time.
And that's like the definition of insanity. Number four,
you aren't in love with direct response.
And I completely understand that there's some people who just, you know,
are better storytellers or better, uh,
cinematographers or movie makers or script writers. Um,
and there's nothing wrong with that, you know? Uh, direct response marketing is,
is definitely a niche thing. And, uh, it's not for everybody. But if,
if you don't, if you, if you don't love marketing, excuse me,
if you don't love direct response,
if you don't love seeing a result from your creative,
then this might be challenging for you in terms of, um, you know,
finding the why, finding the purpose behind what you're doing.
So just wanted to throw that out there. Number five, settling for average.
Okay? So if you're not critical about your own work, you'll never improve, okay?
You've gotta take pride in your work, uh,
even if it's for running ads,
like this is creative work and you should be very proud of yourself to do the
creative, creative work. 'cause not a lot of people can do that, okay?
Analytical, like non-creative people hire you to do creative work.
And so you should constantly be challenging yourself to, uh,
to continue growing. All right? Number six, you don't understand the why.
Alright? This is a big one. And I see a lot of different editors out there,
a lot of different freelancers, a lot of people in positions where, you know,
they're just, they're like, oh yeah, this worked really, really well,
but they don't understand why, and they can't replicate, replicate the success,
right? If you can replicate the success,
then you really understand why it was successful in the first place.
So you're not owning your craft by doing further
analysis or reflection on, you know, your,
your videos or your assets. I, I remember seeing an example of Mr.
Beast talking about how he would just study the crap out of other
viral videos and he would get a group of his homies to do the same thing. And,
um, that's why he blew up.
'cause he was just so tedious and focused on understanding, you know,
what thumb, well, thumbnail works best and da da da.
So it's the same concept with any discipline.
You've got to understand why you're doing it or you're just,
you're just doing it and there's no value in that.
I just like this quote, but I, I'm pretty sure you've heard it,
but when you stop growing, you, you start dying. So it's a very simple concept.
Like you in this life,
you have to constantly be growing or you're just sitting stills.
And I think that's equivalent to dying because our objective here on planet
Earth is to constantly be improving and evolving. And if you're not evolving,
then what's the point? All right? So I'm gonna wrap it up there,
but I'll see you in the next module.
We'll re-talk about direct response marketing and the importance and
examples. It's gonna be kick ass. So I will see you guys there. Cheers.